export const QA =[{question : "What is PonyExpress?", 
    answer: "PonyExpress is a volunteer-based delivery service application that seeks to help communities condense errands like trips to the grocery store. Our service allows people to rely on others in their community to deliver food, and other essentials, thus reducing risk of infection and the spread of COVID-19." },
    
    {question : "Why should I use PonyExpress?", 
    answer: "To reduce the chances of you, or people in your community, getting sick. With the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic, many stores are overflowing with customers and/or require you to spend hours waiting in lines and increasing your risk infection. PonyExpress allows you to reduce the number of these trips you take by helping you create a network of support among your neighbors."
    },
    
    {question :"How is this any different from other grocery-delivery services?", 
    answer: "PonyExpress was designed to foster community action and collaboration during this time of crisis. There is no service charge for placing a request, and your groceries will be delivered by a volunteer from your area. "
    
    },
    
    
    {question :"Is it free to sign up?", 
    answer: "Yes, it is free to sign up and use our platform!"
    
    },
    
    {question :"Will my personal information be released and available to the public?", 
    answer: "When you place a request, the only information that will be posted on the website is your first name, last initial, city, zip code and requested retailer. This way, we can allow couriers to find requests that match their own schedules and trips. Only once a courier has offered to deliver will they receive your address, phone number and shopping list. "
    
    },
    
    {question :"How can I trust the people making deliveries/posting orders? ", 
    answer: "At the current stage, we are unable to enforce the transaction between the requester and the courier. We strongly recommend contacting the courier/requester beforehand to set up a time for dropoff and a payment method. "
    
    },
    
    {question :"What are the qualifications to be a courier?", 
    answer: "Couriers must be over 18 (or over 21 if making a purchase with alcohol). We ask that couriers ensure they are not exhibiting any symptoms relating to COVID-19, including, but not limited to fever, severe shortness of breath and/or chills. They must also acknowledge that they have been symptom free for at least 48 hours; have not, in the past 14 days, participated in gatherings with more than 10 people or traveled through heavily populated areas (ie. airports, train stations, public transit centers, etc); and have not, in the past 14 days, come in contact with someone experiencing symptoms of COVID-19. Couriers must have been social distancing. If any of these conditions are not met to the best of their knowledge, couriers may not make deliveries."
    
    },
    
    {question :"How is payment handled?", 
    answer: "Payment is made from the recipient to the courier after the courier has made the purchase. This means that the courier will temporarily cover the cost of the purchase. We encourage contactless payment, such as Venmo or Paypal. However, both parties can also choose to use cash or any other methods of payment that suit them best."
    
    },
    
    {question :"Who determines how much I have to pay?", 
    answer: "The courier will send a copy of the receipt that shows how much your purchase cost. You are encouraged to tip your courier, as they have likely driven a little out of their way to make the delivery, but tipping is not required."
    
    },
    
    {question :"Can I order alcohol?", 
    answer: "If you are of legal age to purchase and consume alcohol or tobacco, you may include these products in your request. Be sure to mark the box ‘this order contains alcohol’ so that potential couriers will know and be willing to legally purchase these items. "
    
    },
    
    {question :"What do I do if I’m at risk?", 
    answer: "When you’re placing a request, be sure to mark the check box ‘I am part of the elderly or immunocompromised population’, as defined by the CDC, so that your request will be among the first ones shown when someone is offering to deliver. "
    
    },
    
    {question :"Can I use this service if I'm sick?", 
    answer: "If you have tested positive for COVID-19, have been exposed to COVID-19 or are feeling unwell, please refrain from making deliveries and stay at home. However, you may still post requests; just ensure that the delivery and payment methods are contactless in order to minimize the spread of any possible illness."
    
    },
    
    {question :"What is a contactless delivery?", 
    answer: "To minimize the spread of COVID-19, we highly encourage that all deliveries be made contactless. This means that the courier will likely leave your items by your door and let you know that the dropoff has been made (by calling you, texting you or even ringing your doorbell). Once the courier has left, you may open your door and receive your items."
    },
    
    {question :"How can I do a contactless delivery if I’m paying by cash?", 
    answer: "While we strongly encourage you to use a contactless payment system like Venmo or Paypal, you and your courier may also agree to do a cash transaction. In that case, you can leave the cash in an envelope wedged between the doorframe right before your courier is expected to arrive. If you don’t feel comfortable with this, you may get the cash to your courier by leaving it outside your door when they arrive, stepping away from the door and allowing your courier to pick up the money and drop off your items, all while staying at least 6 feet apart."
    
    },
    
    {question :"As a recipient, can I cancel or modify my order?", 
    answer: "If you decide you no longer need your order after someone has offered to deliver, we ask that you let your volunteer courier know ASAP. Furthermore, if you need to modify your order, you must contact your courier with that change independently. All communication after the matching process is in the hands of the users."
    
    },
    
    {question :"As a courier, can I cancel or modify my delivery?", 
    answer: "We encourage couriers not to cancel a delivery, but if you must, please reach out to the recipient as soon as possible. All communication after the matching process is in the hands of the users."
    },
    
    {question :"What should I do if an item is out of stock?", 
    answer: "When placing a request, users will be able to make a choice about out-of-stock items—either dropping them from the order, going with a substitution determined by the courier, or being contacted by the courier for further instruction."
    }
    ]
